dispply.com 2016-04-02

# Terms and Conditions | Dispply – App Advertising and Monetization Platform

Effective Date: March 11, 2015

## General purpose

This Privacy Policy provides you the information about the way that Company collects, stores, uses and discloses Personally identifiable information (information that constitutes personal data on identifiable individuals) of the end-users of Company’s website or Advertising Platform (Users), the information about responsible commercial communications between Users of Advertising Platform, and the main principles of the protection of Users’ Personally identifiable information.

This Privacy Policy is designed to combine both those subject matters and to improve the protection of Users’ Personally identifiable information to prevent risks and failures such as security glitches and hacking, misuse or breaches of personal data exposing the privacy of individuals. 

This Privacy Policy aims to ensure that Users are provided an equivalent level of protection of their Personally identifiable information, and in particular the right to privacy, with respect to the processing of personal data when using Company’s online services.

By using Company’s website or Advertising Platform all Users unambiguously given their consent to this Privacy Policy.

## Collecting Personally identifiable information 

**Company collects but is not limited to:**

  1. information that User provides when registering with Company’s website (including his email address and name, his company’s name, website, country of incorporation);
  2. information that User provides when using the Company’s online services via Company’s website or Advertising Platform, or that is generated in the course of the use of those online services (including the timing, frequency and pattern of service’s use);
  3. information contained in or relating to ACs that User sends through Company’s website or Advertising Platform or sends directly to Company;
  4. information that User provides to Company for the purpose of subscribing to email notifications and/or newsletters.

Company collects Personally identifiable information only when User registers for an Account for the purpose of use Advertising Platform.

**Company doesn’t collect** Users cookies or their information which is then used to send them targeted advertisements to monitor the behaviour of individual users when User surfs the Internet in order to catalogue his interests and build his data profiles

**Company requires** eliminating/reducing personal data or preventing unnecessary and/or undesired processing by offering tools to enhance individuals’ control over their personal data:

  1. Users may change their default Personally identifiable information by sending such request: contact@dispply.com
  2. Before User discloses to Company the personal information of another person, he must obtain that person's consent to both the disclosure and the processing of that personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy

**Company prohibits** the processing of personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade-union membership, and the processing of data concerning health or sex life.

## Use of Information

**Company uses** Users personally identifiable information only:

  1. to performance of a contract to which User is party or in order to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract;
  2. to send User information regarding his Account and Advertising Platform;
  3. to track Users’ compliance with the Terms and Conditions (http://dispply.com/terms-and-conditions) for compliance with a legal obligation to which the User is subject;
  4. for validation, suppression, content improvement and feedback purposes;
  5. According to the legislation when processing of Users’ Personally identifiable information is necessary (i) in order to protect the vital interests of the data subject; (ii) for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller or in a third party to whom the data are disclosed; (iii) processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the controller or by the third party or parties to whom the data are disclosed, except where such interests are overridden by the interests for fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject which require protection under the applicable legislation.

## Protection of Personally identifiable information

Company sets forth a list of technical provisions:

  1. controls authorized requesters by use of restricted request software needed to access Advertising Platform;
  2. protects passwords used to identify individual requesters of Users;
  3. routes requests through a secure electronic mail system that eliminates direct electronic connection to the Advertising Platform;
  4. allows searches only by Advertising Campaign name, and prevent random browsing of the database of the Advertising Platform.
  5. Company doesn’t allow any modification of the ACs, documents or other content provided by User through Company’s website or Advertising Platform. A time stamp certifying the deposit of the document bearing an electronic signature or similar encryption, shall be generated and associated with the document and shall not be alterable. Deletion of such documents also logged.
  6. the Advertising Campaign keeps the logs of any recording, modification and deletion of documents and data.
  7. the data of Advertising Platform regularly backup. The backup with replica of the entire content of the electronic file repository ready for use in case of emergency.
  8. the electronic storage is protected against: (i) any danger of loss or alteration of its integrity; (ii) physical protection against inappropriate temperature and levels of humidity, fire and theft detection systems (iii) against virus attacks, hackers and any other non-authorised access.
  9. the Advertising Platform provides for the migration of data, format and computer environment at intervals sufficient to guarantee legibility and accessibility of documents and data until the end of emergency.

All technical provisions are made in order to protect User’s Personally identifiable information, in particular with regard to the increasing capacity for automated storage and processing of data relating to Users.

## 3rd parties transfer principles

Company provides the implementation of appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect personal data of the Users against accidental or unlawful destruction or accidental loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, in particular where the processing has to be carried out by Company’s Affiliates and involves the transmission of data over a network, and against all other unlawful forms of processing.

When the processing has to be carried out by Company’s Affiliates, Company chooses a processor providing sufficient guarantees in respect of the technical security measures and organizational measures governing the processing to be carried out, and ensures compliance with those measures.

**User be aware that:**

  1. Company’s website and Advertising Platform may contain links to third-party websites. Please be aware that Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of third-party websites. User shall read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Company.
  2. Company uses Tracking links and may use similar techniques to serve content to from our Users and Company’s Affiliates to provide Company’s services. Please be aware that by using Company’s services, Company’s website and Advertising Platform User is giving his unambiguously consent to provide his Personally identifiable information to these 3rd parties and across borders from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world and to the proposed transfer.

## User and Users’ Employees

User’s acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy, in their entirety, shall extend to User’s employees, if any. User guarantees that any of his employees that access User’s Account, or visit Company’s website:

  1. acts in its name and for it and on its behalf;
  2. agrees to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
